[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What comic book does the young man read every day next to the magazine vendor in the movie Watchmen?", "correct_answer": "Tales of the Black Freighter", "incorrect_answers": ["V for Vendetta", "Batman the Long Halloween", "The Adventures of Crispy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the white blood cells, also called leukocytes?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They are cells of the immune system.", "There are five different types of white blood cells.", "There are leukocytes in the lymph."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who distributed the first red ribbon as an anti-AIDS symbol?", "correct_answer": "Paul Jabara", "incorrect_answers": ["Freddie Mercury", "Diana, Princess of Wales", "Elton John"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For this refreshing cocktail you need 2 oz tequila, juice of 1/2 lime and Coca-Cola.  Mix tequila and lime  juice over ice cubes in a the glass. Add cola, stir, and its ready.", "correct_answer": "Mexicola", "incorrect_answers": ["Mojito", "Mimosa", "Monmartre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the war film The Dirty Dozen hit the big screen?", "correct_answer": "1967", "incorrect_answers": ["1968", "1969", "none of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these events is regularly performed only in North Korea?", "correct_answer": "Mass games", "incorrect_answers": ["Senior citizens beauty pageant", "Politicians athletics", "Binoculars football games"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Michael Curtizs movie, Casablanca, who arrives at Ricks club with the priceless letters of transit?", "correct_answer": "Ugarte", "incorrect_answers": ["Sascha", "Ferrari", "Laszlo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the movie in which Alan Rickman portrays a perfumer?", "correct_answer": "Perfume: The Story of a Murderer", "incorrect_answers": ["Perfume: The Scent of Deceit", "Perfume: A Story", "Perfume: A Scent of Passion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first directly-observed collision between two solar system bodies was between Jupiter and which comet?", "correct_answer": "Shoemaker-Levy 9", "incorrect_answers": ["Hale-Bopp", "Schwassmann-Wachmann", "Tuttle-Giacobini-Kresak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This chemical element has a smell similar to garlic and is part of the structure of Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA), the molecule that carries genes.", "correct_answer": "phosphorus", "incorrect_answers": ["iodine", "sulfur", "potassium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the standard Monopoly game set, what is the number of the Chance cards?", "correct_answer": "16", "incorrect_answers": ["17", "20", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "GigaBytes or GB is the measurement used to determine the processor speed.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]